What if I told you you can take one
product image and turn it into five
highquality visual campaign images for
your brand that you can start using
right away? And the crazy part, well,
it's basically for free and you can do
it in under 20 minutes. And I'll show
you exactly how to do it. Hey, welcome
to the channel. Today, we're going to
look at Google's latest model, Gemini
2.5 Flash with Nano Banana. And yes,
that is correct. Because there's a lot
of buzz going around in the designer
world that apparently it's replacing
Photoshop and we can do so much with it
with highquality images that will save
us tons of time. Now, if you look at
campaign images in general, they're
either very time consuming or they can
cost quite a lot of money. So, I'm very
curious to see what it does. But it's
important because if you make those
images, it's very important that you
keep product consistency because we
don't want to have an image that looks
like this in one image and it looks like
that in the next one. We want to have it
product consistent because if you get a
product, you want it to resemble what's
on the screen. So, that I'm going to pay
close attention to. Now, to do that, I'm
going to take this product here, our
fizz drink, and we're going to use this
exact can in five different images or in
five campaign visuals, and we're going
to look at the product consistency and
how we can keep it. And for the first
one, we're going to look at punching
through a wall effect. So, I had this
idea that I want to punch through a wall
and then hold that can. And I think
that's a very powerful image. So, it's a
combination of these three images. What
I did is I found this one here with the
hand punching through the wall. I think
that was a very visually captivating
image. But then I want to add our
product to it. And that's not always
very simple in AI generation because we
don't want to have the can behind the
hand. The brand should be visual. So I
also looked for an image where the can
was sort of turned or the hand was
holding it in the right way. So I added
those three prompts or those three
images to the prompt. And then I
followed it up with the prompt itself
which is make a campaign image of a hand
punching through the wall holding a fizz
can make the wall dark green to the
background. So the bright fizz contrasts
nicely. We have high contrast between
the product and the background. That's
important. Put it in the center of the
image and the logo of the can should be
visible. So no overlap with the hands.
And also that I wanted to mention that
we don't have the fingers over the logo.
So it's important that we really punch
it through. Then I pressed send. And
then we gave it a few seconds and
actually it was quite fast and came up
with this amazing result. So if we look
at this image, the hand is actually
coming pretty nicely through the wall.
The wall itself, the color is exactly
what we wanted and also the contrast is
very nice. If you look at the details of
the hand, that is just fantastic. I mean
it doesn't look AI generated. It looks
very real and very realistic. That is
what we want. Also the can it's almost a
one-on-one copy. So you have to look
very closely and I can barely see any
differences with the product image
itself. So that is already very good. So
I was already pretty happy with this
result and I think we can do a lot more
with it. So let's look at number two
which is going to be punching out of the
ingredients. And that's something which
you see in a lot of campaigns. You see
if it's coffee, you see like beans, you
see the ingredients included with it.
So, for this fizzy drink, I wanted to go
for that lime drink, that lime effect,
that green that contrasts very nicely.
Now, I couldn't really find an image
where I hand punched or was like poking
out of the limes and then holding the
drink. So, if you don't have images
available, you can always go to the
drawing board. What I did is I just
opened up my iPad and sketchbook on
Procreate and I started drawing what I
noticed. So, I wanted to have these
limes at a pile in the bottom and then
again with a hand sort of poking out. I
just made it clear with the different
colors that I wanted to have these three
elements on the green background. And
I'm hoping that I can use this as a
reference picture. Now, don't get
confused. This isn't the final result
yet. This is my sketch, but I wanted to
add it to the prompt to sort of give
advice on how to position the image. So,
for that, I drag the image into Gemini
itself and also the fizzy drink again.
So, I wanted to keep that product there
every single time. So it makes it clear
that we want to use this in this
specific version of the product. Then I
added the following prompt. Make a
professional-grade campaign image 9 by6
ratio. The hand holding the fizz drink.
The logo still visible coming out of the
lime pile. Fresh green limes, solid
green studio background. The fist drink
should be in the center of the view and
it should be realistic. So I gave it a
try and pushed enter. And also after a
few seconds, this is incredibly fast
this model. It came up with this amazing
result. And also that one is actually
quite stunning. So overall, the realism
in this picture was spot on and exactly
what I wanted. Also, the can holding to
the front, that was exactly what we
needed. So that's two for two. Let's go
for number three, which is squeezing the
lemon. Now, there's ways you can go
about this. You can either prompt it
yourself entirely from the idea or you
can do it maybe, let's call it cheap
way, where you take a campaign image
that you found online or something that
inspired you and you throw that into the
font. Now, I'm not entirely sure where
I'm at when it comes to this because
it's a very thin line between just
copying and between getting inspired,
but I think it's a reality that we have
to face in coming with AI. So, I'll just
show you how to do it. You decide
yourself what you want to do with it.
So, here you can see a nice image of a
campaign where a hand is sort of
squeezing a grapefruit on top of a
drink. And I thought that effect could
work really well if you want to use it
for the lime with our fizz drink. So,
for that, I added those two images to
the prompt. And then I followed it up
with the prompt itself, a line being
squeezed above a fizz soda can, studio
background, vibrant green, and studio
lightning. I just wanted to try
something different with like a very
minimal explanation because the picture
itself was already there to give some
guidance. Then I pressed enter and then
it came up with this result here, which
again is a fantastic result. And it's
absolutely insane that you can just get
these results in seconds. Just think
about how long of a setup it would take
and how many tries to get that perfect
line to get it exactly squeezed in the
way dripping in the way that you want.
So this is pretty impressive that you
can actually do it. Now if you want to
change it, maybe you want to add some
levels to it. That is also possible. So
what I've done is I've added prompt
again and I've changed a few things. So
I wanted to put it on a little bit of an
elevated platform just to add some depth
to the slide and some intrigue and then
position some of the limes and
ingredients, some mint leaves around the
can. So, I think that adds for a nice
whole complete visual of the product
that we can use in our campaigns. So,
overall, this one also turned out pretty
cool and I'm very impressed with the
result actually. If you look at the lime
and the details, the squeezing,
everything just looks so perfect and so
clear and realistic. So, that brings us
to number four, which is going to be the
stacking result. And here, I wanted to
go for something a little bit more
unrealistic. I saw this poster here with
those products being balanced in a very
nice way. And I think we can do the same
for the cans. So let's see how it works
with that sort of defying gravity and
stacking those products. So what I've
done is I've added the product itself
and the reference image of the prompt
and then followed it up with the prompt
itself. Make the image of Fiscans
balancing on the fingertip studio
background with that same green hex
color. And then it came up with this
result which I think just looks
fantastic. Just try to do that in
reality. It's almost impossible. You
have to work with some wires. You have
to work with a green screen. Whatever
you want to do. So this is a pretty fast
way that you can actually do it. Now
we've seen the ways that we can do it in
a yeah let's say cheap way where we sort
of copy it. We've seen the ways where we
can do it in a more yeah we draw it
ourselves some concept that we have in
mind but we can also go in depth in the
prompts. So if we want to have something
very specific we can also go in depth in
the prompts and that's what we want to
use in the fifth one. So we want to
create a creative visual image for this
one. And for that I had a visual in mind
where we have a mountains and a
ridiculously large can. So like
mountains size can. And it's somewhere
hidden in the mountain. And I wanted to
be like a very impressive image when you
see it there in the mountain. It's like
a discovery that you can make. So for
that let's have a look at the prompt and
what I've actually wanted. So here I
started typing make the fist can
ridiculously large the side of
mountains. I want it to be stuck in a
snowy mountain like an ancient godly
mega artifact being stuck in the ice for
ages. The branding should be clear and
visible. So also that I want to mention
and the bottom of the can can be in the
glacier or in the mountain buried in the
rocks but the majority of the can should
be visible. The color of the mountains
can be color blue tones while the can
should be vibrant yellow so it nicely
contrast with the background. Then I've
added some pictures of the mountains
that I want. So, some rocks, some snow
that I added with it together with a can
and I just ran it. And this was the
result that it came up with. And I'm
honestly I'm amazed with the result that
it can do. So, if you look at this
image, if you look at the detail, it's
absolutely fantastic. You see the snow,
you see little details of how it's sort
of stuck in the snow for a long time, it
just feels right. So, overall, I'm very
impressed with the results that you can
achieve for this tool. And these are
perfect base visuals for your campaigns.
So, you can start to build text on it,
layer it, you can start to be creative
with it. But this is a good eye-catching
visual that you can create with just a
single product image. Just don't forget
that we started from this single product
image here and we created five different
campaign style images that you can go
crazy with. So definitely let me know
what you think in the comments below. It
will really help me a lot. And if you
want to see how catchy does with these
exact same prompts, make sure to check
the video on the screen right